Guide to the Committee on the Protection of Human Subjects, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1982-1988; Accession 1990-A-065
  - Ginnett: "Team Performance in Aeronautical and Space Environments", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Caruso: "Behavior Problems of Children Referred to Guidance Clinics", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Logan: "Use of Context in Remembering Sentences: Implications for Bilingual Education", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Litt: "Cognitive Mediators of Physical stress", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - Shiller: "An Investigation of the Benefits and Problems of Joint Custody", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 160)
  - Medvene: "Self-Help Groups and Professionals: A Case Study and Survey", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Rodin: "Changes in Taste Responsiveness in Pregnancy", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 162)
  - Herek: "A Neofunctional Theory of Attitudes", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 163)
  - Radford: "Use, Knowledge, and Values of Animals among the Embera Indians of Panama", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 164)
  - Ward: "A Study to Clarify the Relationship between Interparental Conflict and Children's Self-Esteem'', 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 165)
  - Rodin: "Yale Freshman Survey", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - Salovey: "Mood and Self-relevant Thoughts", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - Bybee: "Relationship between Outerdirectedness and Domains of the Self-image in Normal and Mentally Retarded Children", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - McQuire: "Content, Structure and Functioning of Thought Systems", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - Bybee: "The Ideal Self, Self-Image-Disparity and Guilt", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - Singer: "Child and Adolescent Clinical/Community Psychology: Training in Direct Service and Prevention Programming", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Myers: "Yale Epidemiologic Catchment Area Project", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 172)
  - Garner: "Perception of Structure", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - Mishkind, Telgarsky, Timko: "Components of Self-Image", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - Sternberg: "Promoting Individual and Organizational Productivity through Practical Intelligence", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Bybee: "The Development of Self-Image Disparity, Perceptions of the Ideal Self and Guilt in Children'', 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - Gerrig: "Comprehension of Non-Conventional Language", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - Nestle: "Imagination, Empathy, and the Actor: A comparative study of acting and nonacting college students", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - Mishkind: "Gay Men's Health Protective Choices", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - Kessen: "Graduate Research Training in Child Psychology", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - Soloway: "The Cognitive Process Underlying Design", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - Schwartz: "Health Psychology: Clinical and Preventative Research", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Lovett: "Children's Understanding of Random Generating Devices", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Zigler: "Motivational factors in children's performance on the probability learning task", 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Monahan: "Rhythm, recognition, and memory in language", 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Sternberg: "Coping with novelty and human intelligence", 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Anderson: "The Effects of Self-Relevance and Feedback on Intrinsic Motivation", 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - Soloway: "Tutoring Expertise: Human and Computer", 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Soloway: "An analysis of the Code Inspection Process", 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Soloway: "Factors in Effective Computer-Assisted Instruction", 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Lendler: "Factory Worker Interviewing", 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Schwartz: "Assessment of Levels of Emotional Awareness in Normal Individuals", 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Sincoff: "The Development of Verbal Fluency in Elementary and Secondary School-aged Children", 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Trawick: "An Ethnographic Study of Irrigated Terrace Agriculture in an Andean Peasant Economy", 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Kolligan: "The Imposter-Prone Personality: A Causal Analysis", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - Herek: "A Neofunctional Theory of Attitudes", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 196)
  - Crowder: "Infant Musical Preference", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 197)
  - Timko "Mood, stress and physical health", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 198)
  - Rodin: "Aging, Dietary Habits, Social Factors, Stress and Health'', 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 199)
  - Berg: "Age Difference in Strategy by Aptitude Interactions in a Task of Cognitive Maps", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 200)
  - Rabin: "The Role of Experience in Olfactory Discrimination", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 201)
  - Bonnano: "Repression-Sensitization and Self-Monitoring in Relation to Ongoing Thought", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Clayton: "Study of Charitable Appeals", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - Berliner: "Personality Differences in Bulimics and Non-Bulimics", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 204)
  - Prentice: "Personal Preferences", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Martinez: "Male Depression Across the Life Cycle: A Consideration of the Relationship Between Sex Role Indentification, Affiliation and Modes of Depression", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Weissberg: "Promoting Social Competence and Coping Skills in Young Adolescents: Assessment, Intervention and Long-Term Follow-Up", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 207)
  - McGuire: "Content, Structure and Functioning of Thought Systems", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 208)
  - Schwartz: "Craving and Emotional State in the Presence of Desired Food and Fragrance", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 209)
  - Schwartz: "Respiratory Correlates of Fragrance Induced Relaxation", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 210)
  - Ewing: "Reactions to Communications", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 211)
  - Hakuta and Lovett: "Transfer of Metalinguistic and Comprehension Monitoring Skills Across Languages in Bilingual Children", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 212)
  - Livingston: "Social Roles and Psychiatric Disorder Among Adults", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 213)
  - Zigler: "Survey of effects of patterning therapy for retarded children on their parents and nonretarded siblings", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 214)
  - Friedkin: "Technology, Reward Systems, and Changes in the Clerical Workplace'', 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 215)
  - Blodgett: "Teenage Contraception: Belief and Behaviors", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 216)
  - Cattanach: "Psychological and Physiological Reactivity to Stress in Bulimics", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 217)
  - Lehman: "Self-Nurturance and the Binge Eating Aspect of Bulimia", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 218)
  - West: "The Politics of Conditional Aid in Africa's Economic Crisis", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 219)
  - Weissberg: "The Perceptions of Sixth and Ninth Grade Children of Typical Problem Situations'', 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 220)
  - Rodin: "Changes in Taste Responsiveness in Pregnancy", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 221)
  - Samuel: "Two Early Levels of Speech Analysis", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 222)
  - Samuel: "Levels of Processing Speech and Nonspeech", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Zigler: "Social Competence and Psychopathology in Mentally Retarded Adults", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 224)
  - Singer: "Self-Relevant Schemas as Organizing Structure in Word-Recall", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 225)
  - Garner: "Perception of Structure", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 226)
  - Singer: "Child and Adolescent Clinical/Community Psychology: Training in Direct Service and Prevention Programming", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 227)
  - Hodapp: "The Interrelations Between Teachers/Aids and Severely-Profoundly Developmentally Disabled Children", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - Bybee: "The Negative Future Self-Image", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 229)
  - Bybee and Kramer: "Domains of the Ideal Self. Repression-Sensitization.", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 230)
  - Kessen: "Development of visual responsiveness in normal post-adolescents, for comparison with children with precocious puberty", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 231)
  - Zigler: "Cognitive, Motivational and Environmental Determinants of Functioning in Retarded Individuals", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - Zigler: "Effects of Patterning Therapy for Retarded Children on their Parents and Non-Retarded Siblings", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 233)
  - Miller and Lovett: "The Effects of Context on Everyday Social Explanations'', 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Georgaklis: "Romantic Love and Early Father Relationships in Yale Women", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Rosenberg: "Children of Violent Parents; Child Control and Outcome", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Rosenberg: "The Effects of Marital Violence and Discord on Children's Psychological Functioning", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - Young: "Parental and Expert Belief Systems about Infant Development and Infant Care Practices'', 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Berg and Sternberg: "The Development of Practical and Everyday Problem Solving", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - Ansel: "The Development of Reasoning about Evidence", 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - Shiller: "A Study of Investor Behavior", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 241)
  - Crowder: "Recency and the Processing of time in memory", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 242)
  - Miller: "Understanding of Social Conventions: A Developmental Study", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 243)
  - Terrell: "An Investigation of the Interrelations. Among Person Attributes, Coping Efforts, Social Support and Adjustment to College", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 244)
  - Barrios: "Writer's Block: A descriptive study of creative activity", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 245)
  - Ness: "Individual Differences in the Experience of Bodily States and Symptoms", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 246)
  - Speer: "Development of Prosodic Structures in Language Processing", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 247)
  - Singer: "Psychophysiology of Repressive-defensiveness as Process and Cognitive Style", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 248)
  - Schwartz: "Health Psychology: Clinical and Preventative Research", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 249)
  - Rosenberg: "Family Coping and Adaptation to Alzheimer's Diseease", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 250)
  - Rosekind: "The Perception of Sleep and Wakefulness: Subjective and Physiological Determinants", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 251)
  - Harwood: "Quality of Attachment Related to Mother's Implicit Theories of Attachment Behavior and Child-rearing Goals and Practices", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 252)
  - Davis: "A Psychophysiological Study of Repression", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 253)
  - Kessen: "Child Psychology Research Training Grant", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 254)
  - Fillion and Kessen: "Visual Scanning of Media presentations of Gender", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 255)
  - Schaffer: "The Prevalence of Shared Grooming Behaviors and Their Relationship to Health and Well-Being", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 256)
  - Seyb: "Executive Reorganization and the Mainsprings of Institutional Reform", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 257)
  - Evans: "Chronologically Age Appropriate Roles of Mildly and Moderately Retarded Individuals", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 258)
  - Kolligan: "The Imposter-Prone Persoliality", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 259)
  - Wong: "Textbooks, The Social Selection of Educational Knowledge", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 260)
  - Kellert: "Aesthetic Responses to Nonhuman Animals", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 261)
  - Udry: ''Capital and Credit in Northern Nigeria", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 262)
  - Gerrig: "Typicality in Category Recall", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 263)
  - Gerrig: "Comprehension of Non-conventional Language'', 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 264)
  - Gerrig: "Implicit Theories of Intelligence", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Gerrig: "Emotional Mood and Memory", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Breslin: "Achievement Motivation and Discorded Eating Behavior", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Kessen: "Child Psychology Research Training Grant", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Prentice: "Attitudes Toward Social Issues'', 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - Clayton: "Hypothetical Thinking: What might have been and what could be", 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - Clayton: "Thinking about the Past", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 271)
  - Feingold: "Psychology of Creativity and Love", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 272)
  - McGuire: "Generating Cognitive Structures-l", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 273)
  - Perrow: "Organizational Response to AIDS Crisis", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 274)
  - Soloway: ''Teaching Arithmetic by Computers", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 275)
  - Kraus: "Outcomes of Participation In Self-Help Groups Organized By and For Families With Psychiatrically Disabled Family Members", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 276)
  - Dellarosa: "Problem solving in Mathematics and Science", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 277)
  - McGuire: "Content, Structure, and Functioning of Thought Systms", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 278)
  - Telgarsky: "Individual Differences in Responses to Hypnotic Versus Non-Hypnotic Relaxation Techniques", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 279)
  - Weissberg: "Promoting Social Competence and Coping Skills in Young Adolescents: Assessment, Intervention and Long-Tern Follow-Up", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 280)
  - Ewing: "Effects of Conversation on Stimulus Liking", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 281)
  - Ewing: "Reactions to Communications", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 282)
  - Fishman: "Animated Television Effects on Young Children", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 283)
  - Goyette: "Adults' Perception of Children's Eyewitness Testimony'', 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 284)
  - Schab: "Young Adult's Knowledge of And Attitude Toward Time", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 285)
  - Miller: "Culture and Moral Development: A Cross-Cultural Study", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 286)
  - Payne: "The Political Attitudes of Brazilian Industrial Elites in the Transition to Democracy 1974-1986.", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 287)
  - Heard: "Mediating Factors in the Intergenerational Transmission of Aggression", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 288)
  - Gerrig: "Persuasion by Fiction", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 289)
  - Greene: "Real-Time Effects of Naive Physical Beliefs", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 290)
  - Logan: "Beliefs About Gender and Equality: The Social Differentiation of Females and Males", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 291)
  - Stoller: "Sexual Objectification and Perceived Dominance", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 292)
  - Gold: "Short Term Memory and Negative Thought Disorder In Psychiatric Outpatients", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 293)
  - Banaji: "Alcohol and Memory: The Role of Internal Cues", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 294)
  - Novick: "The Yale Research Program for the Cross-Cultural Study of Aids", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 295)
  - Gleicher: "Reactions to Gender and Status", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 296)
  - Myers: "Yale Epidemiologic Catchment Area Project", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 297)
  - Swartz-Gerrig: "Expression of Subtle Differences in American Sign Language'', 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 298)
  - Eastman: "The Beneffectance Bias: A Function of Audience and Self-Esteem", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 299)
  - Hodapp: "Mourning Reactions in Mothers of Different Types of Handicapped Children over Time", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 300)
  - Meisel: "The Economic Consequences of Economists: A Case Study of Columbia in the Post-Frente Nacional Period", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 301)
  - Zigler: "Social Competence and Psychopathology in Mentally Retarded Adults", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 302)
  - Perrow: "Organizational Response to AIDS Crisis", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 303)
  - Luthar: "Evaluation and Validation of Scales Assessing Maternal Narcissism", 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 304)
  - Sternberg: "Managerial Dilemmas: Individual Decision Making in Resolving Value Conflicts", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 305)
  - Zigler: "The Relationship between Selective Attention and Outerdirectiveness in Retarded and Nonretarded Children", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 306)
  - Dellarosa: "Look-Ahead Strategies in Chess", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 307)
  - Weissberg: "The Positive Youth Development Program", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 308)
  - Garner: "Perception of Structure", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 309)
  - Josephs: "Bilingual Lexical Access", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 310)
  - Sincoff: "A Developmental Study of Ambivalence in Adolescence", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 311)
  - Miller: "Perception of Unusual Events", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 312)
  - Miller: "Reasoning of Unusual Events", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 313)
  - Clayton: "Reacting to Stories", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 314)
  - Whooley: "The Influence of Self-Esteem on Degree Of Malignancy in Breast Cancer Patients", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 315)
  - Stoller: "The Perception of Subjects and Objects in Visual Images", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 316)
  - von Hippel: "Senior Research Project on Bulimia", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 317)
  - Labissiere: "Personality and Attitudes", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 318)
  - Gerrig: "The Processing and Representation of Speaker's Meaning", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 319)
  - Schab: "Psychologial Time in the Aged", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 320)
  - Zigler: "Study of Primiparous Parents Utilizing Infant Day Care", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 321)
  - Soloway: "Computer-Based Diagnosis of Student Programming Errors", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 322)
  - Soloway: "A Cognitive Theory of Problem Solving in Complex Detailed Domains", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 323)
  - Schwartz: "Health Psychology: Clinical and Preventative Research", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 324)
  - Friedman: "Content Dependent Inference Processing", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 325)
  - Rodin: "Children's Conceptions of Health and Illness", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 326)
  - Tischler: "Training Program in Mental Health Service Systems Research", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 327)
  - Crowder: "Recency and the Processing of Time in Memory", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 328)
  - Geller: "The Forms and Functions of Internal Representations of Psychotherapy Supervisors", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 329)
  - Kuc: "Improving Ultrasound Attenuation Estimates", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 330)
  - Abelson: "Collaborative Research on Cognitive Processes", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 331)
  - Burack: "Perspective-Taking Abilities of Autistic Subjects", 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 332)
  - Salovey: "Thoughts of Feelings of Runaway Adolescents", 1986-1987` (Box 10, Folder 333)
  - Hopper: "Siblings of Disabled Children", 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 334)
  - Rosenberg: "Friendships in Early Adolescence: Understanding the Role of Friends as a Supportive Resource for Coping with Stressors", 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 335)
  - Speer: "Development of Prosodic Structure in Language Processing", 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 336)
  - Frye: "Computer-Based Investigation of Cognitive Development: Early Arithmetic", 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 337)
  - Rodin: "Health Behaviors and Joining/Quitting Varsity Sports", 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 338)
  - McGuire: "Content, Structure, and Functioning of Thought Systems", 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 339)
  - Dickey: "Children of Alcoholics: An Empirical Study", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 340)
  - Crowder: "Fragrances as Memory Retrieval Cues", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 341)
  - Schwartz: "Health Psychology: Clinical and Preventive Research", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 342)
  - Dellarosa: "Solving Arithmetic Work Problems", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 343)
  - Schwank: "An Interactive AI Teacher for Case-Based Biology Instruction", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 344)
  - Martin: "Cognitive Styles", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 345)
  - Kraemer: "Laboratory Study of Self-Control of Crying in College Students with High and Low Absorption Skill", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 346)
  - Birnbaum: "Weight Schematic vs. Weight Aschematic Women: Differences in Body Image and Self Control", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 347)
  - McGuire: "Generating Thought Structure--2", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 348)
  - Ostrower: "Why the Wealthy Give: A Study of Elite Philanthropy in New York City (Tentative)", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 349)
  - Banaji: "The Effects of Alcohol on Sentence Construction", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 350)
  - Banaji: "Affect and Memory: An Experimental Investigation", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 351)
  - Eicher: "Understanding Fathers and Daughters", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 352)
  - Logan: "Gender and Ehrployrnent Opportunities", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 353)
  - Stoller: "Sexual Objection and Perceived Dominance", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 354)
  - Rodin: "Validity of Subject Waist and Hip Circumference Self-Reported Measurements", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 355)
  - Rodin: "Changes in Taste Responsiveness in Pregnancy", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 356)
  - Silberstein: "Self-Perception, Body Image, and Disordered Eating in College Women", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 357)
  - Weissberg: "Promoting Social Competence and Coping Skills in Young Adolescents: Assessment Intervention and Long-term Follow-Up", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 358)
  - Prentice: "Describing People and Situations", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 359)
  - Tardif: "Aesthetics and the Audition", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 360)
  - Lohse: "Hypnotizability and Character", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 361)
  - Bonanno: "Repression and Auditory Attention", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 362)
  - Weissberg: "The Positive Youth Development Program", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 363)
  - Brand: "Teaching Clinical Obstetrics: A Randomized Trial of Medial Education Through Computer Surveillance and Feedback", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 364)
  - Sachs: "The Political Economy of AIDS in the United States", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 365)
  - Weissberg/Sivo: "Stress, Coping, and Substance Use Among Young Adolescents", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 366)
  - Bybee: "Personality Differences in Eating Disturbed and Non-Eating Disturbed Women", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 367)
  - Cornell: "Factors Affecting the Perception of Physical Symptoms", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 368)
  - Droga: "The Effects of Ego-Task Orientation and Self Esteem on the Beneffectance Bias", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 369)
  - Zigler: "Cognitive, Motivational and environmental Determinants of Functioning in Retarded Individuals", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 370)
  - Sternberg: "Development of Practical Intelligence for School", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 371)
  - Sternberg/Okagaki: "The Effects of Parental Theories of Intelligence on Children's Cognitive Abilities", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 372)
  - Luther: "Vulnerability and Stress-Resistance: A Study of High-Risk Adolescents", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 373)
  - Altemus: "Neurophysiological Correlates of Menstrual Mod Changes", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 374)
  - Hou/Banaji: "Rating Social Information", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 375)
  - Geller: "Neighborhod Attitudes toward Autism and Benhaven", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 376)
  - Kraemer: "Yale Study on Viewpoints in the Medical Profession", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 377)